I'm home...
Welcome home, Akane.
You've been putting in a lot of
overtime lately. Are you all right?
Akane!
Mommy!
It's all right, Mommy's here.
Here, let me wipe you off.
There.
Banzai!
Huh?! She overworked
herself into a high fever
and now she's regressed to childhood?!
Yes.
Mother, how does one go
about repairing a human?
Well, you should probably give
her some medicine and let her rest.
Now that you've taken the
medicine, it's time to go to sleep.
I don't wanna! I'm not sleepy!
I wanna keep talking 'til I get tired!
Naked story time!
Hey! Hey! Mommy! Do you love me?
Of course. More than
anyone in the world.
You mean it?
Same goes for you!
Huh?
How come I'm so big all of a sudden?
Yours are big, too, Mommy!
- You can touch them if you like.
- Really?
Wow, they're so soft!
You don't have to stop at rubbing them.
You can suck them, too.
Bwuhhhhh?!
I'm not gonna nurse on your breasts!
I'm not a baby anymore! I'm a...!
I'm a... I'm a...
Huh?
What am I?
That's right.
I got a cold and I've
been with Mommy all day.
Yeah.
Me and Mom...
Nadeshiko?!
Oh, I'm so relieved.
I'm so sorry for causing such trouble.
It sounds like your mother
was a very kind woman, Akane.
It seems like she doted on you
for longer than might be usual,
and that she really loved you.
I'd never be able to take
the place of a mother like that.
Nah, she wasn't like that.
In actuality, my mom was the type
to just tell you "aw, just sleep it off,"
not someone who'd ever
nurse someone back to health.
That's why...
I'm happy to have you
here by my side, Nadeshiko.
Thank you.
So hey, Nadeshiko...
About your master registration...
I still feel... kinda weird about treating
you like you're property,
but... someday, I promise I'll
find a way to go through with it.
So if you can just... be patient
with me until then, I'd be... happy.
Sure!
I'll just have to keep honing my
sexual techniques until that day comes!
Huh?
You and me...
we'll do so much together!
Yeah, I'll...
Thanks for watching our release!
Brought to you by ToonsHub
need time to think about it...!